Hello friends, my name is Sachin
and today we are again bringing you a new
video, so friends, today we are going to talk
about complete health insurance and today we will review this plan.
Friends, before moving ahead, I
want to tell you that if you are
new to my channel, then please
subscribe to it and press the bell icon
so that you will get all my videos
which are related to insurance
through notifications.
And yes, if you like this video, then
definitely share it with your friends
because knowledge increases by sharing. So
let's start friends, the review of
complete health insurance of IA Se Lootpaat.
So friends, this plan of IA Se number is a
very simple and sober
plan. There are neither many terms
and conditions nor any
exaggerated things given in it. It is a simple plan
and you can understand it very easily.
If I talk about its premium, then
my experience on gas, which is free,
comes quite cheap. If I talk about that
If we choose a plan of Rs 1000000 from any company, at which
premium, then in such a slot, we get a plane of Rs 15 lakhs.
Even many times I have seen that
if we have taken a plan of Rs 5 lakhs from any company, then for the
same premium,
we have got an ICC plane worth up to Rs 10 lakhs. So
friends,
before moving ahead, let me tell you that if you
want me to tell you your premium as well,
how much it costs according to your age and your family, then you
can ask me by WhatsApp or email.
You will get all these details in the description.
So friends, if we talk about the
time limit of this plane, then here you have a
time limit of Rs 5 lakhs to Rs 5000000.
In this, you
can use any rate of your choice. You have all the
options available in it. If we talk about the
expenses before Prince's post graduation, that is, when you were
not admitted to the hospital.  Even before that, whatever
expenses you make can burden you with doctor's fees,
X-rays, medicine bills, interest on loans up to
30 days
before admission. Similarly, if you get
discharged from the hospital, then the
expenses till now can be included in this.
If you want to know more
about prevent hospitalization, then I will give you a
distraction link on the i button here.
Its complete details have been
given to you in it. If we
talk about the room rent limit, then here
you get a single private room
which is sufficient, in which you
can go and get your treatment done from Ram. If we
talk about treatment, there are
150 procedures here which are surgical procedures, there
is a list of them, I will
share its brochure link with you. You
can download it here and go and
see it there. So, these are surgical procedures, in which
you will go in the morning and
return home by evening. So,
you get the expenses of these 150 procedures, we have it there.
Performance should not be above 24 hours.
Here, if we talk about no claim bonus, then in that, a
no claim bonus of ten percent is available,
which takes the maximum up to 50%. If
we talk about reset benefit, this is the same
friends which is the restore benefit.
Here also it is called set the benefit, somewhere it is
called refill, so as soon as your
plan gets exhausted by hundred percent, then
immediately you will be given the same plan again,
like suppose you have taken a
policy of Rs 5 lakh and your 5 lakh
usage is exhausted, within the same year
you will be given ₹5 again in this policy,
but it does not work by getting the same choice,
but suppose someone
in your family gets this disease
and now you want to get treatment above Rs 5 lakh for the same disease, then it will
not be available here.
If we talk about AYUSH treatment, then here you
can take it in I coat, like Ayurveda,
Homeopathy, Siddha, Unani,
then take this type of treatment.
Friends, I want to tell you one more thing,
watch this video completely
because here in the end I am going to tell you such a
thing which is related to 119
and in this policy there is a
special thing which you will not get in every policy
and all these things have been
included in the recent plan, so
I will tell you that
if we talk about ambulance cover here, then
here you will get ambulance cover for ₹15 per horse
performance,
friends, if we look at the
limit here, then any adult of 18 years can
take this plan and there is
no upper age limit in it, that is, if
your parents are 70 years old, 65 years old
or your age is also 70 years,
75 years and if you are fit and fine
then you can wear it, okay, so there is no
limit in this, if you
look in other states then 65 years
is fine, 70 years, 55 years, something different in every film  There is a
limit available but there
is no limit here friends, here
you can cover a new born baby as well.
If a
small child is born in your family and his
parents are already in a policy, then if he is from
191 country then you
can add this in it. Okay, if we
talk about the dependent side, then all your children up to 21 years of age can be
covered under the floater plan in this policy. Friends, there is a good
thing here, a service guarantee, which you will
not get in any company's policy. This is that the
companies guarantee you in return
that your cashless claim will be received within four hours.
If it does not come then the company will charge a
penalty on it. Similarly,
if you have any claim reimbursement,
here you have sent your bills,
performed the Prince Pass, you have got
treatment done at a place where their service was
not available, then also you will get it and
their guarantee is that we will give you that money within 14 days.
If we do not give you
that money then we will give you the  If I
talk about a policy of desperation discount,
then if you take a policy for 2 years at once, then
you will get a
discount of 10% on whatever premium comes, then
suppose you took a policy for 2 years
and there you get a free benefit of ₹3000
or here you will directly get a discount of ₹3000,
then that policy for
2 years will cost you 27 thousand rupees. Here,
if we talk about health checkup coupon,
then friends, here every year you
get help coupons, in this there is a list of some tests,
that test is a lab
technician doctor from any lab will come to your home
and he will test you and the
report of that is sent to your email or by bike
courier to your home, in which it is easy,
your report is done,
your CBC is done, okay, so in this way there are
about seven to eight tests which you will
get free every year in it, friends, there is a
nickel balance program in which
some points are given, like if you participated
in any race, like
Aliya Life Marathon, or swimming
Or you go to the gym, that is, you
maintain good physical activity
and keep yourself fit, then if you
share that detail with them, then they give you some
points and the value of each point is
around 25 paise, so these
points are added to your policy
and whose value becomes approximately two and a half
thousand rupees, if you have added those
points then you can use that thousand rupees
for OPD benefit, for this
you will not have to pay any money,
if suppose you have added those points of ₹ 2000, then
you
can consult a doctor in OPD for two and a half thousand rupees, you can get
medicine and you can sell these bills
to the company and get its debit,
that if we talk here friends and
about channel plan benefits, then there are
some optional benefits in it as well which you
can avail by donating, this is
a normal plan at the back which will give you health
insurance cover when you are a star,
but the company has given some other don't
things here  Which you
can take according to your condition, for example,
if I talk about Mahal Smart Tab-10, then there is
a maternity benefit here, in
which you get a cover of 25 thousand rupees
for normal delivery and 50 thousand rupees for a
section like this, for this you will have to
pay separately, similarly
you will also get the opportunity of OPD, which is
kept separate variant, you can take OPD cover up to ₹5000,
plus there is balance and preventive
health care, as soon as any doctor
asks you for a regular health checkup,
you have got any tests done from the doctor or you have brought
some of your letters, got an
ultrasound done, whatever you have got reported throughout the year, then
here you
can get its debasement from the company, you will have to take it from
Noida, for that in the same way,
if we talk about Mahal Smart Plus, then along with
maternity OPD,
you also get nursing care here,
what happens under nursing care is that if a
mother ever faces such a situation
Here you
need nursing inside the house, so whichever nurse will
come to your house to clear you, then a
15 day benefit is given here, which is ₹2000 to ₹3000 per day,
along with this, hospital is
given in Delhi, which costs Rs.1000 to
₹2000, it depends on which friend you have chosen,
it will be given which will be
valid for one month, if suppose
you study the cost of 20 days
and you spent ₹1000, then ₹20000 will be
given separately in your account, plus there is
conveyance benefit, this benefit is given to friends
and friends, in which
if you have to cover hospitalization for more than 10 days,
then here you are
also given an additional amount of ₹2000 including the amount,
which will be credited to your account,
here you can also take critical illness cover, which
50% will be paid at the same time, which
means that suppose you have a
policy of 10 lakhs, then you
can also take a critical illness cover of Rs 5 lakhs. If
you ever have a critical illness, which
is maintained by the terms and conditions of the policy, there are
about 15 to 18 such things, if
you are diagnosed with any of them, then you simply have to pay
50% of it. This 10 lakh airplane cover of ₹5000 will be
credited to your account, that is,
you will be given cash. So,
friends, you can also take the critical illness cover, for
this also you will have to pay an additional premium.
If you want this in this line, then if we
talk about both the express, then you will get donor express cover of 50
thousand rupees for the member as well as for the member
here, so for that
you have to pay money.
Talking about personal accident benefit, if you have
taken a policy of 10 lakhs, then
you can also take personal accidental cover up to 10 lakhs,
that is, if  If you die in an accident, then
your nominee will get
Rs 10 lakh which will be deposited in their account. So
friends, every policy has
some pros and cons as well.
These cons are
called exclusions in technical terms. So let
us understand that. So
friends, the 2-year waiting period that you see here is
such
diseases which you have declared while taking the policy,
like if someone says that
I have a thyroid problem or someone says that I had a
call letter surgery or someone says that I had a
surgery on my side, then if
you have any such disease which is
ongoing or you are diabetic, then here a
waiting period of 2 years will be imposed on that,
after which you will be able to get cover for that disease, if
you see that there are general and other policies, it is of three
years or four years.
Secondly, if we talk about the waiting
period here, some such diseases can be
cataract.  Be it hernia,
joint replacement, stones,
sinus surgery, in all these places,
in every company, there is a waiting period of almost 2 years,
so here also there is a waiting period of 2
years, there is also a
mandatory waiting period of 30 days that you
cannot get any treatment done, except for
accidental cover, so there is a giver here,
but here a waiting period of 15 days has been
imposed, for Vinod, if
you go for treatment for profit 19k, then
if you take this policy and after 15 days, if something happens to
you that
you become 1971 orbit positive, then
you will get the news there, if friends, if we
talk about the limit of the track here, then the
limit of cataract is 20,000 rupees, but it will
come because cataract is
difficult to detect in people around 60 years or 65 years,
so if you have taken any policy of 5 lakhs, then
you are a giver here.  Now you
can take a cover of Rs 20,000.
I have told you all these limits here in a single submit
and if your policy is above Rs 5 lakh
then come and you will get cover here for Rs 1 lakh.
Talking about the maternity waiting period, as I told you earlier that you
can take a video, there will also be an advisor when
you have kept that document with you for 3 years. It is
not that you have taken it this year and
you want to take maternity cover this year, then
you will not get it. There is a waiting period of 3 years for this.
You will have to keep the document for 3 years if the maternity cover is valid in your policy.
So friends, I
told you in the beginning of the video that you should watch it till the end
because I am going to tell you something
that ICC has added such
documents in their policy keeping in mind 119
and they are not charging anything for this,
so let us discuss what
it is.
So see, this is a special benefit
for 119, the first thing is that you have an
application for this.  Now through it you can
talk to the doctor on the phone and get 24*7
consultation. Friends, if
someone in your family is sick or
you feel that you have this disease
and I am not able to go to the doctor, then
their doctor John is available 20-27, he is
available all day and night, you
can take consultation from him through that app
and it will be free of cost.
You will get consultation twice in every policy and then
if we talk about the waiting period,
which I told you that here the
waiting period of fees has been done, it is
fine for the combination and it is the first
insurance company who brought this
first option, but if
we talk about the no claim bonus here, then
friends, you get a no
claim bonus of 10 percent and if you get any
quoted claim, then you will get it in
your business and whatever
earlier part of your bonus, it will
not be reduced, so you should
understand that your bonus here  But that is just that, if we
talk about home
health care here friends, if you also become positive
and you do not want to
go to the hospital for treatment, I want to be
treated at my home and the same
doctors who are from the hospital should take
care of me, then friends, the facility
is available here which we call health home health
care, so what will you have to do for this,
whenever you become positive, there are
many such
health service providers in the market who provide that service at home, either
you can contact them, they have
full packages of any of their facilities,
you can choose that, then
you can get the treatment done accordingly
or you
can take that service from any health care provider
at your home, if you are some partner for them,
like Max Health Care or Maidan Tak,
they are providing services at home
and if you get cancer there, you will get the
service, you do not have to pay for it,
but if
that service is not available in your area now, then you can do it
in the engagement mode  You can also take it, so
friends, these were some
special benefits of 2019, which they have
added free of cost in their policy
and they will not take any charge for it, till when, till
31 March 2019, if they
feel that till this entire situation is
not controlled, then if we want,
but they will have to take approval of the ID and
if they get this approval, then they
can add this thing in future also, so friends, I
hope you liked this video,
if you liked it, then please
share it with your friends, my
name is Sachin and thank you very much for watching this video.